buycheapsoftware.com 2003-10-01

# BuyCheapSoftware

|     321 Studios   
---  
   Ability Office   
   Adobe   
   Ahead Software   
   AutoDesk   
   Britannica   
   Computer Associates   
   Corel   
   Crystal Decisions   
   DeLorme   
   Executive Software   
   FileMaker   
   FrontRange Solutions   
   Global Marketing   
   Individual   
   Interact Commerce   
   Intuit   
   JASC   
   LapLink   
   Lotus   
   Macromedia   
   Microsoft   
   NetObjects   
   Network Associates   
   Palo Alto Software   
   PeachTree   
   Pinnacle Systems   
   PowerQuest   
   Punch Software   
   Roxio   
   ScanSoft Inc.   
   Symantec   
   Veritas   
|  **BuyCheapSoftware Policies**  
---  
**Privacy Policy**  
  
  * BuyCheapSoftware is committed to protecting all customer privacy. Our business is founded on the trust you place in us. The information we collect is only used to process orders and to provide a personalized shopping environment. You can help us ensure your privacy by not sharing your user name or password with anyone. 
  * **UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL WE EVER RELEASE, SELL, RENT, OR LEASE CUSTOMER INFORMATION TO ANY 3rd PARTY.**
  * **Personal Information:**   
We require only the personal information that is necessary to securely process your online order and for contacting you about your transactions. It is used exclusively for that purpose. If you become a BUYCHEAPSOFTWARE customer, you may receive updated pricelists and special price-reduction offers. If you would prefer not to receive these, please [**Click here**](mailto:sales@buycheapsoftware.com). 
  * **Email Policies:**   
When you purchase online from BUYCHEAPSOFTWARE, we will contact you by e-mail to confirm your order and to update you on the status of your order. We do not release customer email addresses. We contact customers by email to confirm orders, for tech support, and to send updated pricelists. We do not SPAM. 
  * **Customer Satisfaction:**   
BUYCHEAPSOFTWARE is committed to providing all customers with world-class service. We guarantee that you will be satisfied with your purchase. We guarantee that all the software we sell is 100% Authentic. If you have any suggestions, comments, or problems please use the Customer Support link. 
  * **Protection of Information:**   
For your protection our servers use powerful 128-bit encryption technology and Secure Socket Layers (SSL) in all areas where any personal information is requested. BuyCheapSoftware is also certified by VeriSign, the world leader in electronic security. This assures that our site is authentic and that we're employing SSL security. Your account information and order history are kept safe behind our powerful firewall on separate servers. Additionally, access to your personal information is restricted within our company to provide the most security possible. We use every available technology to protect information. To ensure that you also have the most protection available on your computer, be sure to download the latest version Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Communicator. 
  * **Information About Cookies:**   
Cookies are only used to improve your shopping experience. Cookies personalize your shopping experience and they help identify you when you come back to our site. You should set your browser to accept cookies if you wish to add items to a shopping cart. Information collected or stored via cookies includes purchases; log in data, and pricing level, and is kept in a secured area within BUYCHEAPSOFTWARE servers. 
  * **Providing Feedback:**   
Just [**Click here**](mailto:support@buycheapsoftware.com) to send us feedback by e-mail. You can also use any of the links in the “Contact Us” section of the website! 
  * **Corrections in Your Information:**   
Simply call our toll free number (888-999-2611) Open Monday to Friday, 7:30 to 6:00 PM Pacific Standard Time, or send us an [email](mailto:sales@buycheapsoftware.com).
